STEVEN SEMCO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT



719-963-6450



charlesdemar87@gmail.com



www.stevensemco.com

PROFILE

I am a Software Engineer based in the Denver/Colorado Springs metro areas. I am also an artist and muralist, that has multiple murals in the Colorado Springs and Manitou Springs areas. My passion for creation and creativity is a driving factor in both endeavors. My character, determination and work-ethic were forged from many years spent working the line of commercial kitchens.

EDUCATION

Pikes Peak Community College

AS in Computer Science 2020-Present

Ayden-Grifton High School

Graduate 2001-2005

SKILLS

Python

JavaScript

Django

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

React

Bootstrap

GitHub

HTML

CSS

Sass

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE **FELLOW**

General Assembly | Summer 2021

- · Learned web development skills such as HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.
- Created applications using JavaScript and Python.
- · Utilized libraries such as React, Django and Express, as well as database structures like MongoDB and SQL

KITCHEN MANAGER

Frankies Too | 2018-2020

- · Enforcing restaurant policies and resolving staff concerns.
- · Food ordering, inventory and insuring food costs fall within a strict range.
- Training new staff and setting weekly schedules.
- · Cooking in a fast paced, high volume setting.
- Organizing meetings and following a vision for my team.

ASSISTANT KITCHEN MANAGER

Wyatt's Pub and Grill | 2014-2018

- · Opening and closing key holder.
- · Food ordering and inventory.
- · Shift lead and manager on duty responsibilities.
- Training new staff and creating new menu items.
- · Creating daily prep-lists to address kitchen needs and business